[{
	"question": "When does Pakistan celebrate Independence Day?",
	"options": ["A. 14th August", 
		"B. 2nd October", 
		"C. 26th January", 
		"D. 4th July"],
	"answer": "A. 14th August"
},
{
	"question": "Nobel prize is awarded for which of the following disciplines?",
	"options": ["A. Literature, peace and economics", 
		"B. Medicine or Physiology", 
		"C. Chemistry and Physics", 
		"D. All the above"],
	"answer": "D. All the above"
},
{
	"question": "Which city has Introduced first Electronic train technology in pakistan?",
	"options": ["A. Karachi", 
		"B. Lahore", 
		"C. Islamabad", 
		"D. Multan"],
	"answer": "B. Lahore"
},
{
	"question": "First private train in India run between which of the two cities?",
	"options": ["A. Delhi-Lucknow", 
		"B. Delhi-Ahmedabad", 
		"C. Both of the above route", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "A. Delhi-Lucknow"
},
{
	"question": "'LIBRA' an alternative of existing cryptocurrency like bitcoin is being developed by?",
	"options": ["A. Facebook", 
		"B. Google", 
		"C. Microsoft", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "A. Facebook"
},
{
	"question": "In which year was Sports Authority of India established?",
	"options": ["A. 1952", 
		"B. 1967", 
		"C. 1993", 
		"D. 1982"],
	"answer": "D. 1982"
},
{
	"question": "Headquater of International Olympic Committee is situated at?",
	"options": ["A. Athens", 
		"B. Lausanne", 
		"C. Dubai", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "B. Lausanne"
},
{
	"question": "'The Coalition Years' is the autobiography of?",
	"options": ["A. L.K Advani", 
		"B. Pranab Mukherjee", 
		"C. Atal Behari Vajpayee", 
		"D. Sonia Gandhi"],
	"answer": "B. Pranab Mukherjee"
},
{
	"question": "Entomology studies what?",
	"options": ["A. Behavior of human beings",
		"B. Insects",
		"C. The origin and history of technical and scientific terms",
		"D. The formation of rocks"],
	"answer": "B. Insects"
},
{
	"question": "Galileo was an astronomer who",
	"options": ["A. Developed the telescope",
		"B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter",
		"C. discovered that the movement of pendulum produces a regular time measurement",
		"D. All the above"],
	"answer": "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter"
},
{
	"question": "Who is the father of geometry?",
	"options": ["A. Aristotle",
		"B. Euclid",
		"C. Pythagoras",
		"D. Kepler"],
	"answer": "B. Euclid"
},
{
	"question": "Indian player Jude Felix is popular for which sports?",
	"options": ["A. Volleyball",
		"B. Football",
		"C. Hockey",
		"D. Tennis"],
	"answer": "C. Hockey"
},
{
	"question": "Who is the current chief of the world bank group?",
	"options": ["A. Donald Tusk",
		"B. David Malpass",
		"C. Christine Lagarde",
		"D. Jim Yong Kim"],
	"answer": "B. David Malpass"
},
{
	"question": "Who was associated with the creation of pentium chip?",
	"options": ["A. Arun Netravalli",
		"B. Sabeer Bhatia",
		"C. Vinod Dham",
		"D. Vijay Dham"],
	"answer": "C. Vinod Dham"
},
{
	"question": "Which is the first search engine of the internet?",
	"options": ["A. Yahoo",
		"B. Wais",
		"C. Archie",
		"D. Mozilla"],
	"answer": "C. Archie"
},
{
	"question": "In a Database Management System(DBMS) the content and the location of data is identified by ?",
	"options": ["A. Subdata",
		"B. Sequence Data",
		"C. Beta Data",
		"D. Meta Data"],
	"answer": "D. Meta Data"
},
{
	"question": "'.MOV' extensions refer to which kind of file?",
	"options": ["A. Image file",
		"B. Movie File",
		"C. Audio File",
		"D. ZIP File"],
	"answer": "B. Movie File"
},
{
	"question": "Who wrote the famous poem 'The Charge of the Light Brigade'?",
	"options": ["A. Lord Alfred Tennyson",
		"B. Christopher Marlowe",
		"C. Johannes Gutenberg",
		"D. Rene Descartes"],
	"answer": "A. Lord Alfred Tennyson"
}
]
